<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<ModMetaData>
  <name>Minecarts - Get Haul'n Update (Continued)</name>
  <packageId>Mlie.MinecartsGetHaulnUpdate</packageId>
  <author>Compilatron,Ogliss,Parad0x</author>
  <url>https://github.com/emipa606/MinecartsGetHaulnUpdate</url>
  <supportedVersions>
    <li>1.0</li>
    <li>1.1</li>
    <li>1.2</li>
    <li>1.3</li>
    <li>1.4</li>
    <li>1.5</li>
  </supportedVersions>
  <modDependencies />
  <loadAfter />
  <description>[img]https://i.imgur.com/buuPQel.png[/img]
Update of Compilatron,Ogliss,Parad0xs mod https://steamcommunity.com/sharedfiles/filedetails/?id=2540895973

[img]https://i.imgur.com/pufA0kM.png[/img]

[table]
    [tr][td][url=https://dsc.gg/mlie][img]https://i.imgur.com/zdzzBrc.png[/img][/url][/td] [td][url=https://github.com/emipa606/MinecartsGetHaulnUpdate][img]https://i.imgur.com/kTkpTOE.png[/img][/url][/td]
    [/tr]
    [tr]
        [td][img]https://i.imgur.com/WjDSfUn.png[/img][/td]
        [td][img]https://i.imgur.com/Be8E2qJ.png[/img][/td]
    [/tr]
[/table]
	
[img]https://i.imgur.com/Z4GOv8H.png[/img]
Move stuff from A to B with minecarts! Currently an early build, I hope to add more features and improvements later.
	
-- HOW TO USE --

Minecarts are buildings which can be built from the "rails" tab of your architecture menu. Minecarts need rails to function, which can be built in 1 tile wide lines, and with corners.
Minecarts must be given a push to be launched. To launch a minecart, select a nearby pawn, then right click the minecart to open up it's context menu. Then, select the "launch minecart" button. The pawn will walk to the minecart and give it a push to send it on it's way.
Minecarts can carry items in them like transport pods, and can be pushed after the intended items have been loaded.

Get Haul'n update includes revamped vehicle physics, connectable minecart trains and automatic pickup and dropoff points, along with general balance changes and a glossy new look.
	
Credit to Mic for the minecart textures; They did a great job :D
	
Also a special thanks to everyone in the RimWorld discord server who had to go through the agonizing pain of explaining to me how to mod RimWorld.

Update as of 2021, Fixed by Ogliss, Mlie and uploaded by Parad0x. New content planned partially based off old plans.

Credits to Compilatron for allowing this and original creation of the mod.

Free for anyone to update, take over or otherwise maintain.

[img]https://i.imgur.com/PwoNOj4.png[/img]
[list]
[*] See if the the error persists if you just have this mod and its requirements active.
[*] If not, try adding your other mods until it happens again.
[*] Post your error-log using [url=https://steamcommunity.com/workshop/filedetails/?id=818773962]HugsLib[/url] or the standalone [url=https://steamcommunity.com/sharedfiles/filedetails/?id=2873415404]Uploader[/url] and command Ctrl+F12
[*] For best support, please use the Discord-channel for error-reporting.
[*] Do not report errors by making a discussion-thread, I get no notification of that.
[*] If you have the solution for a problem, please post it to the GitHub repository.
[*] Use [url=https://github.com/RimSort/RimSort/releases/latest]RimSort[/url] to sort your mods
[/list]

[url=https://steamcommunity.com/sharedfiles/filedetails/changelog/2998019751][img]https://img.shields.io/github/v/release/emipa606/MinecartsGetHaulnUpdate?label=latest%20version&amp;style=plastic&amp;color=9f1111&amp;labelColor=black[/img][/url]</description>
  <modVersion IgnoreIfNoMatchingField="True">1.5.0</modVersion>
</ModMetaData>